http://www.nowlcms.org/privacy-policy

Northwest District of the Lutheran Church Missouri SynodPrivacy NoticeLast updated May 18, 2020Keeping the faithThe Northwest District of the Lutheran Church Missouri Synod (“the district,” “we,” “us,” etc.) is a nonprofit Christian organization that provides services and resources to The Lutheran Church Missouri Synod (“LCMS”) congregations, LCMS schools, LCMS ministries, LCMS Recognized Service Organizations and constituents located in Oregon, Alaska, Washington, Idaho, and one congregation in Hong Kong so that they may live as fully committed followers of Jesus. We offer information and opportunities to gather, in person and online, to celebrate our beliefs and faith. We also help maintain, in support of The Lutheran Church Missouri Synod (“the Church,” “LCMS,” or “synod”), a nationwide placement database for LCMS Rostered workers, looking for guidance with their careers within the Church, along with continuing education resources for those leaders. The Northwest District also supports workers who are on the Minister of Religion – Ordained and Minister of Religion – Commissioned rosters of the LCMS.These efforts, to connect constituents with one another – or to jobs and education – require us to collect personal information about Web site visitors, registrants, teachers, pastors, and church leaders who use our tools and services. When it comes to handling your personal information, we want to reassure you that it’s being handled in a responsible way. This Privacy Notice is part of our effort to achieve that.When you visit our Website (http://nowlcms.org/) to search for congregations, events, resources, or guidance; share your faith-based experiences on our story page; or sign up to receive our monthly newsletters and information on our podcasts, you will share your personal information in various ways. Sometimes we collect it directly from you. Other times, we use technology to automatically collect personal information. We may also receive your personal information directly from the LCMS.  In all cases, you can be confident that we will handle your personal information lawfully and faithfully, with an eye toward protecting your rights. We also want to give you the necessary tools and options to manage your personal information as you see fit.This Notice applies to our Website and any sites or services that display these terms. It does not apply to any website, mobile app, or service that does not display or link to this Privacy Notice or that contains its own privacy notice. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not use our Website or services. By accessing the Website or using our services, you agree to this Notice.How we collect personal informationWe may collect personal information from you directly or indirectly. When you fill out a form on our Website (to sign up for our newsletter or podcasts, for example), you provide personal information directly to us. Other times, personal information is collected automatically as you use our Website. In addition, we also may receive personal information from third parties with whom we partner.We collect personal information when you provide itWhen you subscribe to our newsletter or register an account with us, you will provide personal information that may include your name and email address. When you create an account with us, you will also create a username and password, information that on subsequent visits helps us confirm your identity and makes it easier to use our services.You may also provide personal information to us at events or by phone and even through old-fashioned mail when you correspond with us. Besides collecting your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address, we may also take or receive photographs of you at conferences and other events we either sponsor or help moderate that we share on our Website or through social media posts.We collect personal information from third-party sourcesWe may collect personal information about you (that you have provided) from certain third party vendors, such as our software provider ACS Technologies who helps us with our data management efforts and donation and registration payment processor Vanco who provides information about donations made to us and event registration. We also use Constant Contact, an emarketing firm, to manage our database of constituents and disseminate our newsletters and podcast information. Note that when we share your personal information with a third party, we require that third party to protect the information consistent with this Notice and limit use of the information to performing the services they provide to us.As you are likely aware, we work with other LCMS Districts across the United States, and the LCMS, to help maintain a national database of openings for internships, paid positions, and educational opportunities within the LCMS. Constituents who are seeking those kinds of opportunities will voluntarily share personal information that may include their names, contact information (mailing addresses, email addresses, phone numbers), gender, and education level. That information is maintained by the LCMS and is shared with LCMS seminaries, LCMS schools, LCMS congregations, LCMS districts, and LCMS Recognized Service Organizations (“RSO”) in the United States.We also may collect personal information from online social networks if you take part in a public conversation, for example, by posting on Facebook. We may collect personal information when you click “Share This” or “Like” buttons or otherwise use social media buttons or plug-ins. We sponsor social media pages and posts, and we moderate conversations and virtual meetings on those platforms. We also encourage sharing via social media “throwback” photos of constituents to encourage celebrations and remembrances of faith. We recommend that you become familiar with the privacy policies of any social network you visit or use as their terms of use and privacy policy govern any information you post on those networks.The payment processors we work with for conferences and other events we organize or support, typically gather your personal information when you pay to attend them. That information includes but is not limited to your name, address, e-mail address, and credit card information. The information shared with us is limited to your name, email and a very limited amount of financial information (the last 4 digits of your card, the type of card used (Visa®, Mastercard®, etc.) and the name on the card) so that we may confirm your registration.  It should be noted that the payment processor is not covered by this policy, but by the payment processors’ privacy policy and terms of use so please refer to those when using that service.We collect personal information using automated technologiesSometimes personal information is collected by automated technologies and shared with us when visitors navigate through our Website. We may track your browsing actions and log your IP address.Those automated collection technologies – such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts – are used by us to analyze trends, administer the Website, and track users’ movements around the Website. A “cookie” is a small text file that is stored on an individual’s computer and downloaded to the computer or mobile device when he or she visits a website. Cookies then send information back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes that same cookie.Cookies perform different jobs, such as allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improving a user’s experience on a website or with an app. We use different types of cookies on our Website:Required Cookies. These cookies are necessary for our Website to function properly and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually set in response to actions made by you that amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in, or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of our Website will not work if you block these cookies.Performance and Functional Cookies.  Performance and functional cookies allow us to count visits and sources of traffic on our Website so we can measure and improve its performance and functionality. They help us know which pages of our Website are most and least popular and how visitors move around the Website.Social Media Cookies. These cookies allow you to share information using social media sharing buttons (such as the Facebook “Like”) on social networks like Facebook, LinkedIn, Instagram, or Twitter. This information may be used by the social media network to deliver targeted advertising to you.Our Website uses the following cookies:Cookie nameDomainPurposeDurationDrupal.tableDrag.showWeightNowlcms.orgRemembers user customizations1 yearSessionNowlcms.orgRemembers login23 daysgaNowlcms.orgGoogle Analytics2 yearsgaidNowlcms.orgGoogle ID24 hoursHas_jsNowlcms.orgJavascript supportSessionIf you wish to opt out of allowing certain cookies, you may do so by changing your browser settings so that cookies from our Website cannot be set. Please note that if you delete, block, or otherwise restrict cookies, then use a different computer or Internet browser, you will need to renew your cookie management choices. The same thing applies if you refuse cookies by turning them off in your Internet browser: If you change Internet browsers, you will need to make the same setting change in your new browser.Also note that certain cookies are necessary for our Website to function properly. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of our Website will not work if you block them. These cookies do not store any information that identifies you directly but are based on identifying your browser and internet device.We will not knowingly collect information from anyone younger than 16 yearsOur resources and services are not intended for use by anyone younger than 16 years old, and we will never knowingly collect personal information from anyone that young. If we become aware that personal information of anyone younger than 16 has been provided to us, for any purpose, we will delete the information from our files.Do not track requestsSome browsers offer a “Do Not Track” privacy preference or setting. Generally, when a user turns on the Do Not Track Signal, their browser sends a message to websites requesting that the user not be tracked. Our Website currently does not respond to “Do Not Track” signals.How we use personal informationWe know your personal information is important to you, so we want to be transparent about our use of it. As mentioned above, we use personal information primarily to send newsletters to Website visitors who have chosen to receive them and help constituents find career and educational opportunities within the Church.We also collect and use this information to provide easier, quicker access to our Website and secure the information you have provided. As constituents navigate through the Website, their movements will be tracked and analyzed. Using this information allows us to improve their experiences. We also use personal information:To send communications through email.To respond to support requests or respond to enquiries.To provide access to and maintain the security and integrity of the Website.To provide updates regarding the Website and its resources.To comply with legal and regulatory requirements applicable to our church and internal policies for maintaining records.To protect all parties in the event of disputes.To comply with court orders and legal processes, and to enforce our Terms of Use and this Privacy Notice.For any other legal, business, or marketing purposes that comply with the practices described in this Notice.When we share personal informationOnce your personal information is collected, as detailed above, we may share it with third parties for various reasons. As mentioned above, we help connect constituents with career and educational opportunities that may be available within our District or other districts within the Church. We also use Google Analytics to study how users interact with our Website and keep it up and running. This allows us to see what areas of our Website are most engaging and provide relevant and useful information to our constituents.If you make a public post, other users may see itIf you make a post on a third-party social media site, such as Facebook, or by identifying us in your social media feed by tagging us using a hashtag (#) or “at” (@), your personal information may be publicly available and is subject to the privacy policies of those third-party social media sites. As a reminder, this Notice describes how we will treat your personal information once it is in our possession.We recommend you review the privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit to understand the data collection and practices of that third party.We may share feedback you provide to usWe want to hear how we’re doing. If you have suggestions for improving our resources and services, ideas for faith-based topics you’d be interested in learning about, or expanding the reach of our ministry, we want those as well. Please be aware that any feedback relating to our services on our Website or social media channels may be publicly shared.Eventual successors may access informationIn the event of a merger or reorganization of all or a portion of our assets, any user information owned or controlled by us may be among the assets transferred to third parties as successors in interest. As part of this type of transaction, we reserve the right to transfer or assign your personal information to third parties. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, or as otherwise agreed to by you, the use and disclosure of all transferred user information will be subject to this Notice.We need to comply with legal requirementsWe may disclose your information to government authorities or other third parties if any lawful circumstances arise, including when:You have given us permission to share your information.We are required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order.We believe, in our sole discretion, that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect against fraud, or to protect our property, constituents or other rights or those of other users of the Website, the Church, third parties, or the public at large.We believe that you have misused the Website by using it to attack or gain unauthorized access to a system or to engage in spamming or other conduct that violates applicable laws or our Terms of Use.How we secure personal informationWe have implemented industry-accepted administrative, physical, and technology-based security measures to protect against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, and alteration of personal information in our systems.While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, no method of transmission over the Internet or form of electronic storage is 100 percent secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Questions or concerns about security or privacy protocols.If you have received unwanted or unsolicited e-mail from us or purporting to be sent by us, please forward a copy of that e-mail with your comments to admin@nowlcms.org for our review. If you feel that any of our privacy practices or security standards detailed in this Privacy Notice have been violated, you may contact us (see Contact Us at the end of this Notice for additional details).Your RightsWe understand that you want to protect and control your personal information. This section details how you may review, update, correct, or delete that information.Viewing or updating your personal information You may update your name, username, password, email address, and email preferences by accessing your account on the Website.Deactivating your accountYou may deactivate your account at any time. To deactivate your account, please send an email to admin@nowlcms.org with “Deactivate Account” in the subject line. Upon receiving your request, we will deactivate your account and delete personal information where allowed or required by applicable law.Opting out of promotional emailsIf you do not wish to receive promotional e-mails from us, you may follow the unsubscribe process at the bottom of the promotional e-mail you received or by emailing us at admin@nowlcms.org . Please keep in mind that you still may receive transactional e-mails from us (such as e-mails related to the completion of your registration, correction of user data, password reset requests, reminder e-mails you have requested, and other similar communications) that may be necessary for us to make the Website available to you or respond to your enquiries and support requests.Request for information and identity verification requirementYou may request information about what personal information we have about you and with whom we have shared that information.  To make a request, please contact admin@nowlcms.org with “Personal Information Request” in the subject line and provide full details about your request, including your contact information and anything you believe is relevant. We will provide a response to an access request within the timeframes required by law. If we cannot substantively respond in a timely manner, we will notify you and provide the reason for the delay.Under certain circumstances, we may not fulfill your request, such as when doing so would interfere with our regulatory or legal obligations, when we cannot verify your identity, if your request involves disproportionate cost or effort, or when the law allows us to retain that information. But we will respond to your request within a reasonable time, as required by law, and provide an explanation.The law requires us to verify that any request submitted was made by someone with the legal right to access the information. Therefore, before accessing or divulging any information pursuant to a data access request, we may request that you provide us with additional information so we can verify your identity and legal authority, particularly when the information provided with the request is insufficient to confirm legal authority and/or identity.European Economic Area, Switzerland, United Kingdom, or Canada rightsWe currently do not target our resources or services to individuals outside of the United States, specifically in the European Economic Area (including Switzerland and the United Kingdom), nor Canada. We do not intend for our Website to be accessed by anyone in those jurisdictions. In the event we begin to tailor our Website resources and services to people in those geographic areas, we will update these terms to ensure we reflect any additional rights reserved under applicable laws. Those updates will be made available within this Privacy Notice, in accordance with those regulations.California Consumer RightsThe California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides specific rights to those who live in California. However, the Northwest District of the Lutheran Church Missouri Synod currently is not subject to the law. If our business practices and future expansion changes so that the California law applies to us, we will update these terms to ensure we reflect any additional rights reserved under applicable laws. Those updates will be made available within this Privacy Notice, in accordance with those regulations.UpdatesThis Privacy Notice will be updated to reflect our personal information handling practices.  We reserve the right to amend this Notice at any time, for any reason, without additional notice to you, other than through posting the updated Privacy Notice on our Website. We invite you to return to this page to ensure you are informed of any updates we make about how we collect, use, and protect personal information. You can see when this Privacy Notice was last updated by checking the “last updated” date displayed at the beginning of this Notice.Contact UsIf you have questions about the way we handle personal information, please contact us:Northwest District of the Lutheran Church Missouri Synod1700 NE Knott StreetPortland, OR 97212(888) 693-5267
Our TeamTerms of UsePrivacy Policy
Follow us:
Toll Free: 888-693-5267
Phone: 503-288-8383
Fax: 503-284-2785
Contact us
1700 NE Knott Street
Portland, OR 97212
get directions >>
Web Design by Sync Interactive
Confirm password *
What primary ministry are you associated with? (optional)
Select state
All statesAlaskaArizonaBritish ColumbiaCaliforniaChinaFloridaGeorgiaGermanyGuineaHong KongIdahoIndianaMinnesotaMissouriNebraskaNew MexicoNon-GeographicOregonRegionalTexasUtahWashingtonWisconsin
Select city
AberdeenAlbanyAlbuquerqueAlbuquerqueAll CitiesAlohaAnchorageAnderson IslandArlingtonAshlandAshtonAstoriaAstoriaAuburnAustinBattle GroundBeavertonBellevueBellinghamBendBenton CityBingenBlackfootBlaineBoiseBonney LakeBoringBremertonBrewsterBrookfieldBrookingsBuckleyBuhlBurienBurleyBurnsCaldwellCannon BeachCascadeCentral PointChehalisChesireChesireChugiakClark ForkCoeur d'AleneCoos BayCopper CenterCorneliusCorvallisCottage GroveCoulee CityCouncilCyberspaceDamascusDaytonDeer ParkDelano BayDelta JunctionDes MoinesEagle PointEast WenatcheeEatonvilleEdenEdmondsEmmettEphrataEstacadaEugeneEverettFairbanksFederal WayFilerFlorenceForest GroveFt. WayneGearhartGeorgeGig HarborGitanyowGoodingGrahamGrand CouleeGrand MoundGrangevilleGranite FallsGrants PassGreshamHaileyHappy ValleyHermistonHillsboroHomedaleHomerHood RiverIdaho FallsIrvineJeromeJohn DayJunction CityJuneauKatyKenaiKenmoreKennewickKenoKentKimberlyKingstonKlamath FallsKlickitatLaGrandeLaPineLaceyLake OswegoLake StevensLakebayLakeviewLeavenworthLebanonLewistonLincoln CityLivermoreLoganLongviewLynnwoodMarlinMarysvilleMcCallMcMinnvilleMedfordMercer IslandMeridianMesaMill CreekMiltonMilwaukeeMolallaMonmouthMonroeMontereyMoses LakeMountain HomeMountlake TerraceMt VernonMt. AngelMullanMyrtle PointNampaNeah BayNew PlymouthNewportNorth BendNorth BonnevilleOak HarborOakridgeOberamerrgauOdessaOgdenOkanoganOlympiaOntarioOregon CityOrovilleOrtingOsburnOsoOsoyoosPacificPalmerPascoPhilomathPhoenixPleasant HillPocatelloPort AngelesPortlandPrince GeorgeProsserPullmanPuyallupQuincyRathdrumRedmondReedsportRentonRepublicRepulse BayRichlandRigbyRogue RiverRoseburgRupertSaint PetersSalemSalt Lake CitySan AntonioSandpointSandyScappooseSeaTacSeabeckSeasideSeattleSeaviewSelahSequimSeveral locationsSewardShanghaiSheltonSheridanSherwoodSiguiriSilverdaleSilvertonSistersSitkaSnohomishSoda SpringsSoldotnaSpirit LakeSpokaneSpokane ValleySpringfieldSt AnthonySt HelensSt LouisSt. PaulStanleyStaytonSterlingSunnysideSutherlinSweet HomeTacomaTampaTanacrossThe DallesTigardTillamookTonasketTroutdaleTualatinTwin FallsVancouverVenetaVirtual ConferenceWaldportWalla WallaWarner RobinsWashougalWasillaWeiserWenatcheeWendellWilsonvilleWoodburnYakima
Select ministry
All MinistriesAll Nations Lutheran ChurchAll Saints Lutheran Church and Rise and Shine PreschoolAmazing Grace Lutheran Church and Christian SchoolAnchorage Lutheran ChurchAscension Lutheran Church and ECE CenterBeautiful Savior LutheranBeautiful Savior Lutheran Church and Early Learning CenterBeautiful Savior Lutheran Church and PreschoolBeautiful Savior Lutheran Church and PreschoolBeautiful Savior Lutheran Church and Preschool & Early Learning CtrBeautiful Savior Lutheran Church and Preschool/KBeautiful Savior Lutheran and Anchor Lutheran SchoolBeautiful Savior PreschoolBethany Lutheran ChurchBethel Lutheran ChurchBethel Lutheran ChurchBethlehem Lutheran ChurchBethlehem Lutheran ChurchBethlehem Lutheran Church and PreschoolBethlehem Lutheran Church and PreschoolBethlehem Lutheran Church and PreschoolBethlehem Lutheran Church and SchoolCalvary Lutheran ChurchCalvary Lutheran ChurchCalvary Lutheran ChurchCalvary Lutheran ChurchCalvary Lutheran Church and PreschoolCalvary Lutheran Church and Preschool/KCamp LutherhavenCamp Lutherwood OregonCamp OrtohaCamp PerkinsChapel of the Cross Lutheran ChurchChrist Community Lutheran ChurchChrist Evangelical LutheranChrist Lutheran ChurchChrist Lutheran Church and PreschoolChrist Lutheran Church and SchoolChrist Our Redeemer Church and Little Lambs PreschoolChrist the King Lutheran ChurchChrist the King Lutheran Church and SchoolChrist the Savior Lutheran Church and PreschoolChrist the Vine Lutheran Church and ECE CenterChurch of all NationsClover Trinity Lutheran Church and SchoolCommunity of Christ - Memorial Lutheran Church and PreschoolCommunity of Christ - St Lukes LCMS and Preschool/KConcordia International SchoolConcordia Lutheran ChurchConcordia Lutheran Church and Little Lambs PreschoolConcordia Lutheran Church and PreschoolConcordia Lutheran SchoolConcordia Lutheran SchoolConcordia UniversityCrown of Life LutheranDenali Lutheran Church and PreschoolEbenezer Evangelical Lutheran ChurchEmmanuel Lutheran ChurchEmmaus Lutheran ChurchEpiphany Lutheran Church and Arrowhead Inglemoor PreschoolEritrean Evangelical LutheranEvergreen Lutheran Church and PreschoolFaith Deaf Lutheran ChurchFaith Evangelical Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran Church and Precious Little Lambs PreschoolFaith Lutheran Church and PreschoolFaith Lutheran Church and PreschoolFaith Lutheran Church and PreschoolFaith Lutheran Church and SchoolFaith Lutheran PreschoolFaithful Savior Min. LutheranFirst Evangelical Lutheran ChurchFirst Korean Lutheran ChurchFirst Lutheran ChurchFirst Lutheran ChurchFirst Lutheran ChurchForest Hills Lutheran SchoolFriendship Celebration Church and PreschoolFunny River Community Lutheran ChurchGloria Dei Lutheran ChurchGood Shepherd LutheranGood Shepherd LutheranGood Shepherd Lutheran Church and PreschoolGood Shepherd Lutheran and Little Lambs PreschoolGood Shepherd Lutheran and Little Lambs PreschoolGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran Church and Life! Lutheran SchoolGrace Lutheran Church and PreschoolGrace Lutheran Church and PreschoolGrace Lutheran Church and Preschool/ChildcareGrace Lutheran Church and Preschool/DaycareGrace Lutheran Church, ECC,
Day School and High SchoolHoly Cross Lutheran ChurchHoly Cross Lutheran ChurchHoly Cross Lutheran Church and Sonshine ECCHong Kong International SchoolHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran Church and SchoolHope Lutheran Church and SchoolHope Lutheran Church o/f DeafImmanuel Lutheran ChurchImmanuel Lutheran ChurchImmanuel Lutheran ChurchImmanuel Lutheran ChurchImmanuel Lutheran ChurchImmanuel Lutheran Church and PreschoolImmanuel Lutheran Church and PreschoolImmanuel Lutheran Church and PreschoolImmanuel Lutheran Church and School/CDCIn Faith Dependent Lutheran ChurchIn His Hands Preschool (Memorial)King of Glory Lutheran ChurchKing of Kings Lutheran Church and Preschool/KLCMS International CenterLamb of God Evangelical Church and PreschoolLamb of God Lutheran ChurchLamb of God Lutheran Church and Zion SchoolLight of Christ Lutheran Church and PreschoolLittle Lambs Lutheran CDCLiving Savior Lutheran and PreschoolLiving Water Lutheran ChurchLutheran Chapel on the HillLutheran Church of St Paul and PreschoolLutheran Church of the Atonement and
Christian PreschoolLutheran Church of the Cross and Sunbeams Lutheran SchoolLutheran Indian MinistriesLutheran Latino MinistriesLutheran Ministry Services NorthwestLutherwood Camp and Retreat CenterMacleay Conference & Retreat CenterMakah Lutheran ChurchMeadowlane Christian SchoolMekane Yesus Lutheran ChurchMemorial Lutheran ChurchMessiah
Lutheran Preschool and Child CareMessiah Lutheran ChurchMessiah Lutheran ChurchMessiah Lutheran ChurchMessiah Lutheran ChurchMessiah Lutheran Church and Little Lambs PreschoolMessiah Lutheran Church and PreschoolMount Rainier Lutheran High SchoolMt Calvary Lutheran ChurchMt Drum Lutheran ChurchMt Olive Lutheran Church and PreschoolMt Olive Lutheran Church and PreschoolMt Olive Lutheran Church and Preschool/DaycareMt Zion Lutheran ChurchNew Hope Lutheran and Early Childhood CenterNew Vision Lutheran ChurchNorthwest District LCMSNorthwest Parish Nurse MinistriesOur Redeemer Lutheran ChurchOur Redeemer Lutheran Church and Noah's Ark PreschoolOur Redeemer Lutheran Church and PreschoolOur Redeemer Lutheran Church and PreschoolOur Savior Lutheran ChurchOur Savior Lutheran ChurchOur Savior Lutheran ChurchOur Savior Lutheran ChurchOur Savior Lutheran Church and Noah's Ark PreschoolOur Savior Lutheran Church and PreschoolPeace Lutheran ChurchPeace Lutheran ChurchPeace Lutheran ChurchPeace Lutheran ChurchPeace Lutheran ChurchPeace Lutheran Church and Little Doves Preschool/KPeace Lutheran Church and PreschoolPeace Lutheran Church and PreschoolPeace Lutheran Church and SchoolPilgrim Lutheran ChurchPilgrim Lutheran ChurchPilgrim Lutheran Church and PreschoolPilgrim Lutheran Church and SchoolPleasant Hill LutheranPortland Lutheran Elem/Mid School/ High SchoolPrecious in His Sight CDCPrince of Peace LutheranPrince of Peace Lutheran Church and PreschoolPrince of Peace Lutheran Church and Preschool/KRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran Church and PreschoolRedeemer Lutheran Church and PreschoolRedeemer Lutheran Church and PreschoolResurrection Lutheran ChurchResurrection Lutheran ChurchRiver of Life Lutheran Church and Little Fishes PreschoolSalem Lutheran ChurchSaving Grace LutheranSeattle Lutheran High SchoolShepherd o/t Hills Lutheran Church and PreschoolShepherd o/t Hills Lutheran Church and PreschoolShepherd of the MountainsShepherd of the ValleyShepherd of the ValleyShepherd of the Valley Lutheran ChurchSt James Lutheran ChurchSt James Lutheran Church and Memorable Moments Day Care CntrSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran Church and Preschool/Christian DaycareSt John Lutheran Church and Preschool/KSt John Lutheran Church and SchoolSt John Lutheran Church and SchoolSt Luke Lutheran ChurchSt Matthew LutheranSt Matthew Lutheran ChurchSt Michael Lutheran ChurchSt Paul Evangelical LutheranSt Paul Lutheran ChurchSt Paul Lutheran Church and SchoolSt Paul Lutheran Church and SchoolSt Paul's Lutheran Church and SchoolSt Peter Lutheran ChurchSt Peter the FishermanSt Peter's Lutheran Church and PreschoolSt Timothy Lutheran ChurchStar of the North LutheranSterling Lutheran ChurchThe Lutheran Church of the Good ShepherdTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran Church and PreschoolTrinity Lutheran Church and PreschoolTrinity Lutheran Church and PreschoolTrinity Lutheran Church and PreschoolTrinity Lutheran Church and PreschoolTrinity Lutheran Church and SchoolTrinity Lutheran Church and SchoolTrinity Lutheran Church and SchoolTriumphant King Lutheran Church and King's Children PreschoolValley of Peace LutheranVietnamese Lutheran Church of the MasterVietnamese Mission StationWest WA LC of the DeafXrossway Lutheran MinistriesZion Christian SchoolZion Evangelical LutheranZion Evangelical Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran Church and Early Childhood Lrng CenterZion Lutheran Church and Little Lambs Learning CenterZion Lutheran Church and Open Arms Child Dev CtrZion Lutheran Church and PreschoolZion Lutheran Church and Preschool/KindZion Lutheran SchoolZion-Emmanuel Lutheran
Describe your Position(s) at your current ministry (optional): Order
Weight for row 1
-4-3-2-101234
Weight for row 2
-4-3-2-101234
Weight for row 3
-4-3-2-101234
Weight for row 4
-4-3-2-101234
Weight for row 5
-4-3-2-101234
Search Groups to Join (optional)
Select state
All statesAlaskaArizonaBritish ColumbiaCaliforniaChinaFloridaGeorgiaGermanyGuineaHong KongIdahoIndianaMinnesotaMissouriNebraskaNew MexicoNon-GeographicOregonRegionalTexasUtahWashingtonWisconsin
Select city
AberdeenAlbanyAlbuquerqueAlbuquerqueAll CitiesAlohaAnchorageAnderson IslandArlingtonAshlandAshtonAstoriaAstoriaAuburnAustinBattle GroundBeavertonBellevueBellinghamBendBenton CityBingenBlackfootBlaineBoiseBonney LakeBoringBremertonBrewsterBrookfieldBrookingsBuckleyBuhlBurienBurleyBurnsCaldwellCannon BeachCascadeCentral PointChehalisChesireChesireChugiakClark ForkCoeur d'AleneCoos BayCopper CenterCorneliusCorvallisCottage GroveCoulee CityCouncilCyberspaceDamascusDaytonDeer ParkDelano BayDelta JunctionDes MoinesEagle PointEast WenatcheeEatonvilleEdenEdmondsEmmettEphrataEstacadaEugeneEverettFairbanksFederal WayFilerFlorenceForest GroveFt. WayneGearhartGeorgeGig HarborGitanyowGoodingGrahamGrand CouleeGrand MoundGrangevilleGranite FallsGrants PassGreshamHaileyHappy ValleyHermistonHillsboroHomedaleHomerHood RiverIdaho FallsIrvineJeromeJohn DayJunction CityJuneauKatyKenaiKenmoreKennewickKenoKentKimberlyKingstonKlamath FallsKlickitatLaGrandeLaPineLaceyLake OswegoLake StevensLakebayLakeviewLeavenworthLebanonLewistonLincoln CityLivermoreLoganLongviewLynnwoodMarlinMarysvilleMcCallMcMinnvilleMedfordMercer IslandMeridianMesaMill CreekMiltonMilwaukeeMolallaMonmouthMonroeMontereyMoses LakeMountain HomeMountlake TerraceMt VernonMt. AngelMullanMyrtle PointNampaNeah BayNew PlymouthNewportNorth BendNorth BonnevilleOak HarborOakridgeOberamerrgauOdessaOgdenOkanoganOlympiaOntarioOregon CityOrovilleOrtingOsburnOsoOsoyoosPacificPalmerPascoPhilomathPhoenixPleasant HillPocatelloPort AngelesPortlandPrince GeorgeProsserPullmanPuyallupQuincyRathdrumRedmondReedsportRentonRepublicRepulse BayRichlandRigbyRogue RiverRoseburgRupertSaint PetersSalemSalt Lake CitySan AntonioSandpointSandyScappooseSeaTacSeabeckSeasideSeattleSeaviewSelahSequimSeveral locationsSewardShanghaiSheltonSheridanSherwoodSiguiriSilverdaleSilvertonSistersSitkaSnohomishSoda SpringsSoldotnaSpirit LakeSpokaneSpokane ValleySpringfieldSt AnthonySt HelensSt LouisSt. PaulStanleyStaytonSterlingSunnysideSutherlinSweet HomeTacomaTampaTanacrossThe DallesTigardTillamookTonasketTroutdaleTualatinTwin FallsVancouverVenetaVirtual ConferenceWaldportWalla WallaWarner RobinsWashougalWasillaWeiserWenatcheeWendellWilsonvilleWoodburnYakima
Select ministry
All MinistriesAll Nations Lutheran ChurchAll Saints Lutheran Church and Rise and Shine PreschoolAmazing Grace Lutheran Church and Christian SchoolAnchorage Lutheran ChurchAscension Lutheran Church and ECE CenterBeautiful Savior LutheranBeautiful Savior Lutheran Church and Early Learning CenterBeautiful Savior Lutheran Church and PreschoolBeautiful Savior Lutheran Church and PreschoolBeautiful Savior Lutheran Church and Preschool & Early Learning CtrBeautiful Savior Lutheran Church and Preschool/KBeautiful Savior Lutheran and Anchor Lutheran SchoolBeautiful Savior PreschoolBethany Lutheran ChurchBethel Lutheran ChurchBethel Lutheran ChurchBethlehem Lutheran ChurchBethlehem Lutheran ChurchBethlehem Lutheran Church and PreschoolBethlehem Lutheran Church and PreschoolBethlehem Lutheran Church and PreschoolBethlehem Lutheran Church and SchoolCalvary Lutheran ChurchCalvary Lutheran ChurchCalvary Lutheran ChurchCalvary Lutheran ChurchCalvary Lutheran Church and PreschoolCalvary Lutheran Church and Preschool/KCamp LutherhavenCamp Lutherwood OregonCamp OrtohaCamp PerkinsChapel of the Cross Lutheran ChurchChrist Community Lutheran ChurchChrist Evangelical LutheranChrist Lutheran ChurchChrist Lutheran Church and PreschoolChrist Lutheran Church and SchoolChrist Our Redeemer Church and Little Lambs PreschoolChrist the King Lutheran ChurchChrist the King Lutheran Church and SchoolChrist the Savior Lutheran Church and PreschoolChrist the Vine Lutheran Church and ECE CenterChurch of all NationsClover Trinity Lutheran Church and SchoolCommunity of Christ - Memorial Lutheran Church and PreschoolCommunity of Christ - St Lukes LCMS and Preschool/KConcordia International SchoolConcordia Lutheran ChurchConcordia Lutheran Church and Little Lambs PreschoolConcordia Lutheran Church and PreschoolConcordia Lutheran SchoolConcordia Lutheran SchoolConcordia UniversityCrown of Life LutheranDenali Lutheran Church and PreschoolEbenezer Evangelical Lutheran ChurchEmmanuel Lutheran ChurchEmmaus Lutheran ChurchEpiphany Lutheran Church and Arrowhead Inglemoor PreschoolEritrean Evangelical LutheranEvergreen Lutheran Church and PreschoolFaith Deaf Lutheran ChurchFaith Evangelical Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran ChurchFaith Lutheran Church and Precious Little Lambs PreschoolFaith Lutheran Church and PreschoolFaith Lutheran Church and PreschoolFaith Lutheran Church and PreschoolFaith Lutheran Church and SchoolFaith Lutheran PreschoolFaithful Savior Min. LutheranFirst Evangelical Lutheran ChurchFirst Korean Lutheran ChurchFirst Lutheran ChurchFirst Lutheran ChurchFirst Lutheran ChurchForest Hills Lutheran SchoolFriendship Celebration Church and PreschoolFunny River Community Lutheran ChurchGloria Dei Lutheran ChurchGood Shepherd LutheranGood Shepherd LutheranGood Shepherd Lutheran Church and PreschoolGood Shepherd Lutheran and Little Lambs PreschoolGood Shepherd Lutheran and Little Lambs PreschoolGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran ChurchGrace Lutheran Church and Life! Lutheran SchoolGrace Lutheran Church and PreschoolGrace Lutheran Church and PreschoolGrace Lutheran Church and Preschool/ChildcareGrace Lutheran Church and Preschool/DaycareGrace Lutheran Church, ECC,
Day School and High SchoolHoly Cross Lutheran ChurchHoly Cross Lutheran ChurchHoly Cross Lutheran Church and Sonshine ECCHong Kong International SchoolHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran ChurchHope Lutheran Church and SchoolHope Lutheran Church and SchoolHope Lutheran Church o/f DeafImmanuel Lutheran ChurchImmanuel Lutheran ChurchImmanuel Lutheran ChurchImmanuel Lutheran ChurchImmanuel Lutheran ChurchImmanuel Lutheran Church and PreschoolImmanuel Lutheran Church and PreschoolImmanuel Lutheran Church and PreschoolImmanuel Lutheran Church and School/CDCIn Faith Dependent Lutheran ChurchIn His Hands Preschool (Memorial)King of Glory Lutheran ChurchKing of Kings Lutheran Church and Preschool/KLCMS International CenterLamb of God Evangelical Church and PreschoolLamb of God Lutheran ChurchLamb of God Lutheran Church and Zion SchoolLight of Christ Lutheran Church and PreschoolLittle Lambs Lutheran CDCLiving Savior Lutheran and PreschoolLiving Water Lutheran ChurchLutheran Chapel on the HillLutheran Church of St Paul and PreschoolLutheran Church of the Atonement and
Christian PreschoolLutheran Church of the Cross and Sunbeams Lutheran SchoolLutheran Indian MinistriesLutheran Latino MinistriesLutheran Ministry Services NorthwestLutherwood Camp and Retreat CenterMacleay Conference & Retreat CenterMakah Lutheran ChurchMeadowlane Christian SchoolMekane Yesus Lutheran ChurchMemorial Lutheran ChurchMessiah
Lutheran Preschool and Child CareMessiah Lutheran ChurchMessiah Lutheran ChurchMessiah Lutheran ChurchMessiah Lutheran ChurchMessiah Lutheran Church and Little Lambs PreschoolMessiah Lutheran Church and PreschoolMount Rainier Lutheran High SchoolMt Calvary Lutheran ChurchMt Drum Lutheran ChurchMt Olive Lutheran Church and PreschoolMt Olive Lutheran Church and PreschoolMt Olive Lutheran Church and Preschool/DaycareMt Zion Lutheran ChurchNew Hope Lutheran and Early Childhood CenterNew Vision Lutheran ChurchNorthwest District LCMSNorthwest Parish Nurse MinistriesOur Redeemer Lutheran ChurchOur Redeemer Lutheran Church and Noah's Ark PreschoolOur Redeemer Lutheran Church and PreschoolOur Redeemer Lutheran Church and PreschoolOur Savior Lutheran ChurchOur Savior Lutheran ChurchOur Savior Lutheran ChurchOur Savior Lutheran ChurchOur Savior Lutheran Church and Noah's Ark PreschoolOur Savior Lutheran Church and PreschoolPeace Lutheran ChurchPeace Lutheran ChurchPeace Lutheran ChurchPeace Lutheran ChurchPeace Lutheran ChurchPeace Lutheran Church and Little Doves Preschool/KPeace Lutheran Church and PreschoolPeace Lutheran Church and PreschoolPeace Lutheran Church and SchoolPilgrim Lutheran ChurchPilgrim Lutheran ChurchPilgrim Lutheran Church and PreschoolPilgrim Lutheran Church and SchoolPleasant Hill LutheranPortland Lutheran Elem/Mid School/ High SchoolPrecious in His Sight CDCPrince of Peace LutheranPrince of Peace Lutheran Church and PreschoolPrince of Peace Lutheran Church and Preschool/KRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran ChurchRedeemer Lutheran Church and PreschoolRedeemer Lutheran Church and PreschoolRedeemer Lutheran Church and PreschoolResurrection Lutheran ChurchResurrection Lutheran ChurchRiver of Life Lutheran Church and Little Fishes PreschoolSalem Lutheran ChurchSaving Grace LutheranSeattle Lutheran High SchoolShepherd o/t Hills Lutheran Church and PreschoolShepherd o/t Hills Lutheran Church and PreschoolShepherd of the MountainsShepherd of the ValleyShepherd of the ValleyShepherd of the Valley Lutheran ChurchSt James Lutheran ChurchSt James Lutheran Church and Memorable Moments Day Care CntrSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran ChurchSt John Lutheran Church and Preschool/Christian DaycareSt John Lutheran Church and Preschool/KSt John Lutheran Church and SchoolSt John Lutheran Church and SchoolSt Luke Lutheran ChurchSt Matthew LutheranSt Matthew Lutheran ChurchSt Michael Lutheran ChurchSt Paul Evangelical LutheranSt Paul Lutheran ChurchSt Paul Lutheran Church and SchoolSt Paul Lutheran Church and SchoolSt Paul's Lutheran Church and SchoolSt Peter Lutheran ChurchSt Peter the FishermanSt Peter's Lutheran Church and PreschoolSt Timothy Lutheran ChurchStar of the North LutheranSterling Lutheran ChurchThe Lutheran Church of the Good ShepherdTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran ChurchTrinity Lutheran Church and PreschoolTrinity Lutheran Church and PreschoolTrinity Lutheran Church and PreschoolTrinity Lutheran Church and PreschoolTrinity Lutheran Church and PreschoolTrinity Lutheran Church and SchoolTrinity Lutheran Church and SchoolTrinity Lutheran Church and SchoolTriumphant King Lutheran Church and King's Children PreschoolValley of Peace LutheranVietnamese Lutheran Church of the MasterVietnamese Mission StationWest WA LC of the DeafXrossway Lutheran MinistriesZion Christian SchoolZion Evangelical LutheranZion Evangelical Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran ChurchZion Lutheran Church and Early Childhood Lrng CenterZion Lutheran Church and Little Lambs Learning CenterZion Lutheran Church and Open Arms Child Dev CtrZion Lutheran Church and PreschoolZion Lutheran Church and Preschool/KindZion Lutheran SchoolZion-Emmanuel Lutheran
Select category
All CategoriesChurch Administration & FinanceCongregationsDistrict Task ForcesEarly ChildhoodFamily Ministry & YouthLeadershipMissionalPartnersSchoolsTheology
keyword
All StaffCenter for Prayer & RenewalChaplainsChurch/School Financial LeadersCircuit 14Circuit 19 Peninsula CircuitCircuit 23Circuit 9Circuit VisitorsCongregational Life Cycle ForumDeacons & Supervisors [NOW District]Disability Awareness Task ForceDisaster Preparedness/Response ForumDistrict Board of DirectorsDistrict DCEsEarly Childhood Education MinistryEthnic Ministries Task ForceEthnic Ministry ForumInland Empire Pastors ConferenceIntentional Interim MinistryLutheran Latino MinistriesMAP--West CoastMinistry to MilitaryMission Training CenterMission Training Center InstructorsMissional Communities Best Practices ForumModeratorsNOW District Executive StaffNOW District Seminary StudentsNOW District Vice PresidentsNew Pastors 2013Oregon Pastors ConferencePresidents Mission Advisory GroupPuget Sound Pastors ConferenceSLSISocial Media TipsSouth Idaho Pastors ConferenceSynod Convention DelegatesWA/AK LLL/LHMWebsite AdministrationWebsite Tips and TricksWinkel Conference Circuits 7 & 9
You can choose up to five groups.
